NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents on Microfilm 6167 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents on Microfilm
1933-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York Univeristy (NYU) Tamiment Library
National Coat and Suit Recovery Board
6167 mf
2.11 cubic feet
19 microfilm reels
Records, microfilm.
5825289
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Coat and Suit Industry National Recovery Board came about for the purpose of assuring that garments were made in accordance with the Fair Labor Standards. The 'union label' was placed on garments that were made by workers who were not working excessive hours and who were being paid fair hourly wages.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6168 mf: NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents (copy 2) on Microfilm
Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Arbitration, Industrial; Collective labor agreements; National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board (U.S.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 35 (New York, N.Y.); National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board (U.S.); Tamiment Library
5825289
- 1933 (Oct.-July) 1934 -- Cleveland Office: Records/Correspondence - Frank A. Garvey (Reel 2)
- Fact Finding Commission, Philadelphia - June 22, 1934 (Reel 3)
- Label Coats Resolutions - 1935 - re: Baltimore Market (Reel 4)
- National Retail Dry Goods Assn. 1934-1935 (Reel 5)
- Work Stoppages 1933-1935 -- Strikes - Notification (Reel 6)
- Convention Pictures - 1941 (Los Angeles) (Reel 7)
- Meeting - May 1941 - Convention Reports (Reel 8)
- Meetings 1942 (Reel 9)
- Meetings 1942 (Reel 10)
- Meeting - National Executive Board 1951 (Reel 11)
- Pacific Coast Region - 1947-1959 (Reel 12)
- Boston Region -- 1957-1960 (Reel 13)
- Executive Board Members of Nat'l. Board of the Coat & Suit Industry -- to 1970 (Reel 14)
- Meetings - Nat'l. Exec. Board 1961 (Reel 15)
- Meeting: Nat'l. Exec. Board - Pictures, Publicity, Correspondence Feb.-Mar. 1966 (Reel 16)
- Meeting: Nat'l. Exec. Board - 1970 (Reel 17)
- Tariffs & Trades - Exports - GATT: 1961-1968 (Reel 18)
- FTC - Philadelphia to 1945 (Reel 19)
- FTC Exhibit Information Data (Reel 20)